{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/41006/":{"taskOID":41006,"originalTaskOID":41006,"setID":763,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500200,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the hot tub or spa for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the hot tub or spa for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1317,"questionDisplayText":"Hot tub or Spa Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of hot tub or spa would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1319,"questionDisplayText":"Hot Tub or Spa Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size hot tub or spa?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two person","answerDisplayText":"Two person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Four person","answerDisplayText":"Four person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5751,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Six person","answerDisplayText":"Six person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2150,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eight person","answerDisplayText":"Eight person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6287,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ten person","answerDisplayText":"Ten person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1320,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Hot Tub or Spa","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will this hot tub or spa be indoors or outdoors?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1322,"questionDisplayText":"Features Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features you want in your hot tub.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2279,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exercise swim jets","answerDisplayText":"Exercise swim jets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","answerDisplayText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1746,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cushioned head rests","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned head rests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Tub freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4524,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ozonator","answerDisplayText":"Ozonator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1365,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chemical feeders","answerDisplayText":"Chemical feeders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4935,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Programmable filtration cycles","answerDisplayText":"Programmable filtration cycles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4696,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Pivoting seats","answerDisplayText":"Pivoting seats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500200,"questionDisplayText":"Already Purchased:","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Have you already purchased the hot tub or spa for this project?","shortQuestionText":"Have you already purchased the hot tub or spa for this project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1317,"questionDisplayText":"Hot tub or Spa Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of hot tub or spa would you like?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Free-standing (portable)","answerDisplayText":"Free-standing (portable)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1176,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Built-in (in-ground)","answerDisplayText":"Built-in (in-ground)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1319,"questionDisplayText":"Hot Tub or Spa Size","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size hot tub or spa?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two person","answerDisplayText":"Two person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Four person","answerDisplayText":"Four person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5751,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Six person","answerDisplayText":"Six person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2150,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eight person","answerDisplayText":"Eight person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6287,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ten person","answerDisplayText":"Ten person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6554,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Two person","answerDisplayText":"Two person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2610,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Four person","answerDisplayText":"Four person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5751,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Six person","answerDisplayText":"Six person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2150,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Eight person","answerDisplayText":"Eight person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6287,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Ten person","answerDisplayText":"Ten person","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1320,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Hot Tub or Spa","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will this hot tub or spa be indoors or outdoors?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3207,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Indoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4476,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor hot tub/spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1322,"questionDisplayText":"Features Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the features you want in your hot tub.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2279,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exercise swim jets","answerDisplayText":"Exercise swim jets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","answerDisplayText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1746,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cushioned head rests","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned head rests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Tub freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4524,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ozonator","answerDisplayText":"Ozonator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1365,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chemical feeders","answerDisplayText":"Chemical feeders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4935,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Programmable filtration cycles","answerDisplayText":"Programmable filtration cycles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4696,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Pivoting seats","answerDisplayText":"Pivoting seats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2279,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Exercise swim jets","answerDisplayText":"Exercise swim jets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3603,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Lights","answerDisplayText":"Lights","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6088,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","answerDisplayText":"Stereo and integrated speakers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1746,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cushioned head rests","answerDisplayText":"Cushioned head rests","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubbles","answerDisplayText":"Bubbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Tub freeze protection","answerDisplayText":"Tub freeze protection","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4524,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Ozonator","answerDisplayText":"Ozonator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1365,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Chemical feeders","answerDisplayText":"Chemical feeders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4935,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Programmable filtration cycles","answerDisplayText":"Programmable filtration cycles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4696,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Pivoting seats","answerDisplayText":"Pivoting seats","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1839,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck","answerDisplayText":"Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/41006/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":41006,"taskName":"Hot Tub or Spa - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Hot Tub or Spa","xmTaskDescriptor":"Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":133,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Hot Tub Spa hottub sauna","textMessagingName":"Inst Hot Tub","rolloverLongDesc":"These systems often include a tub, jets, heater, pump, bubblers \u0026 filters. Set up usually includes both electrical \u0026 plumbing issues. Usually handled by spa specialists.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes stand-alone wooden or fiberglass tubs.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Hot Tub or Spa.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":45,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Hot Tub or Spa Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Hot Tub or Spa - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Hot Tub or Spa Installation Project","urlName":"Hot-Tub-or-Spa-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Hot Tub \u0026 Spa Installation Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Hot,Tub,Spa,hottub,sauna,jacuzzi,tubs","emcCategoryOid":-12044,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":763,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}